Help on the velocity derived quantities
###########################################

This step allows to display velocity derived quantities such as the averaged 
velocity field, the contour map of the intensity of the velocities, the stream-
lines or the vorticity field or velocities along a cross-section.
 
The vorticity is computed as dv/dx-du/dy and saved in outputs.dir/vorticity.out.

For the extraction of velocities along a cross-section, input manually with the 
mouse the beginning and ending points of a cross-section. Velocities are interpolated
 for 11 points distributed along the segment and saved in outputs.dir/cross_vel.out. 

The last button of the tool bar allows making some editorial changes. Clicking on it
 opens the plot browser and the property editor, where color, colormap, markers, lines, 
etc… can be changed.

The button Save plot allows saving the current figure onto jpeg format.
