Help on the discharge computation
###########################################

During that step, one can input a filter on the velocity magnitude. A threshold on 
the minimum and the maximum of the velocity intensity can be inputted using the GUI, 
and the averaged-filtered velocity field is displayed. Using the GUI, one can adjust 
the filtering parameters until the result is satisfactory. 

The averaged velocity field is stored in the file outputs/average_vel.dat. 
The file contains 6 columns: X, Y, U, V, SDU, SDV, where SDU stands for the standard 
deviation of U and SDV the standard deviation of V.