Help on the quality check and averaging
###########################################

The computational grid defines the points in the image coordinate system where 
the IAs and the SAs are centered. The grid is defined by its 4 corners and the 
number of steps. 

Input the 4 corners localization by clicking on Input corners, and then by clicking 
on the image. The corners should be inputted clockwise or counterclockwise. Then 
input the number of steps between the points 1 and 2 and the points 3 and 4, and 
the number of steps between the points 2 and 3 and the points 4 and 1. The grid is 
displayed when the button Compute grid  is pushed.

  1                  2
  X------------------X
  |                  |
  |                  |
  |                  |
  |                  |
  X------------------X
  4                  3

The coordinates of the nodes of the grid are stored in the file outputs/grid.dat.
