Help on the discharge computation
###########################################

If a cross-section bathymetry is available, a discharge can be computed. Input the 
bathymetry file. It must be a 3 columns file containing:
  - X
  - Y
  - h, the water depth at the position X,Y

Example:
-1	10.4	0
-0.5	10.4	0
0	10.4	0
0.188	10.4	0
0.5	10.4	0.12
0.8	10.4	0.23
1	10.4	0.2
1.2	10.4	0.16
1.5	10.4	0.24
1.75	10.4	0.23
2	10.4	0.32
2.25	10.4	0.35
2.5	10.4	0.36
2.65	10.4	0
3	10.4	0
3.5	10.4	0
4	10.4	0

Then input the ratio k between depth-averaged velocity and surface velocity. This ratio is 
usually considered close to 0.85. A discharge is then computed using the Velocity Area Method:
for each point of known bathymetry, the program averages the 4 closest velocity estimates and 
projects it on the streamline direction. This averaged velocity is multiplied by k, by the water 
depth and by the distance related to the considered bathymetry measurement. 

The so computed discharge is stored in the file outputs/discharge.dat. 
The 3D view of the cross-section bathymetry and the surface velocities is displayed.

