Help on the grid parameterization
###########################################
PIV algorithm calculates the correlation between the interrogation area (IA) 
centered on a point aij in the first image and the IA centered at point bij 
in the second image taken with a interval time of δt seconds. 

The IA size defines the spatial resolution of the measurement.
 
The correlation coefficient R(aij,bij) is a similarity index for the grey-scale 
intensity of a group of pixels contained in the two compared IAs.

Correlation coefficients are only computed for points within a searching area (SA).
The SA size has to be selected so that the displacement of tracer patterns from the 
first image is contained within the SA of the second image. Consequently, the SA size 
is commensurate with the expected range of velocities of the river. 
  
Display 2 corrected images by clicking on Display 2 images and asses the size of
the IA and of the SA regarding the flow and tracers properties. 

The IA shape is a square. Its size must be an even number. 

The SA is defined by 4 lengths: Sim, Sip, Sjm, Sjp, where i and j are the 2 axis of 
the image and m and p stands for minus and plus. Sim is so the length of the SA from 
the center of the IA following the i axis in the negative direction.
  ----------------------------
  |             |            |
  |             |Sim         |
  |             |            |
  |     Sjm     |       Sjp  |
  ----------------------------
  |             |            |
  |             |            |
  |             |            |
  |             |Sip         |
  ----------------------------

The Min Correlation edit zone allows inputting a threshold for the minimum value of 
the correlation coefficient that is used. If the maximum R is lower to that threshold, 
the vector is considered as spurious.
Clicking on create IA and SA display a corrected images and an IA (in red) and a SA 
(in blue) localized in the center of the image. Check if the sizes of the IA and SA are OK.
 

The parameters of the LSPIV analysis are stored in outputs/PIV_param.dat.